<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$214,900.00 ]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[7160 E Lakeshore Drive]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Walkerville]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[MI]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[49459]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Lakefront Cabin House will be on the market until March 30th. If no interest, it will be turned into weekly vacation rental. Please contact]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[Lakefront Cabin House will be on the market until March 30th. If no interest, it will be turned into weekly vacation rental. Please contact us at 616-836-1059. Completely remodeled home located on beautiful School Section Lake. The house has all new sliders, windows, siding, water heater, furnace, A/C unit and much more. The house is located on 3 separate lots that offer a total of 150ft of lake frontage. House also had a detached 2 story garage. This house is a must see!æPlease email dviening@gmail.com]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://fsbo.com/listings/listings/show/id/182449/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$174,900.00 ]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[138 Pepperstone Drive]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Mocksville]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[NC]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[27028]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Quiet neighborhood close to shopping and services with excellent interstate access A one and a half story home with main floor master and large]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[Quiet neighborhood close to shopping and services with excellent interstate access A one and a half story home with main floor master and large bonus/bedroom/office area upstairs. 30 x 16 Great Room. Recently updated with new floor, stainless steel appliances and granite counter top in kitchen, many new light fixtures and fresh paint throughout.æBright eat in kitchen, Large living/dining area, Two zone HVAC, Generous attic for storage, Back patio, 2 car garage with workbench alcove, 1.3 acre flat lot with mature landscaping, Equipment/workshop, Conveniently located in a quiet neighborhood 5 minutes from Interstate 40 and Walmart.]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://fsbo.com/listings/listings/show/id/182443/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$689,000.00 ]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[456 Fairfield Avenue]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Stamford]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[CT]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[6902]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Beautiful three family house for sale in a family friendly neighborhood. Main first floor apartment consists of large kitchen, living room, three ]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[Beautiful three family house for sale in a family friendly neighborhood. Main first floor apartment consists of large kitchen, living room, three bedrooms, bathroom plus half bath and laundry room. (Approximately 1700 square feet). In addition there are two one bedroom sunny apartments on the second floor which can be accessed from back porch or front common hallway. (Approximately 800 square feet each apartment.) Hardwood floors throughout. Large attic can be accessed from common hallway. This is perfect for the owner to live on the main floor while collecting income from all other apartments which can help with the mortgage. Finished walk out basement(in-law apartment) approximately 1000 square feet. Off-Street parking available for four cars. Large backyard with patio and porch. Property being sold "As Is". Convenient to bus line and I-95. Close to both Stamford and Old Greenwich train stations. Walking distance to restaurants, park, and Long Island Sound. Around the corner from Innis Arden Golf Course. Seven minute car ride to downtown Stamford and Old Greenwich. House is a good investment opportunity or owner occupied with investment income. Don't let this opportunity pass you by. Must See. Make appointment today!]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://www.forsalebyowner.com/listing/456-Fairfield-Ave-Stamford-CT/5874106bb0f839fc578b4567]]></listingurl>
	</node>
</data>
