<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$170,000.00]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[18303 Piers End Drive ]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Noblesville]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[IN]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[46060]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[This beautiful garden home is a quiet end unit on a prime lot that backs up to green space and woods. Home features 2 bedrooms/2 bath plus a sunroom. Includes vaulted ceilings, island in kitchen, built in book cases and gas fireplace. ]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[This beautiful garden home is a quiet end unit on a prime lot that backs up to green space and woods. Home features 2 bedrooms/2 bath plus a sunroom. Includes vaulted ceilings, island in kitchen, built in book cases and gas fireplace. All appliances stay including washer & dryer. The Gardens at Stone Harbour is a maintenance free community including lawncare, trash removal and common water sewer.]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://fsbo.com/listings/listings/show/id/182613/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$465,000.00]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[24 Wintonbury Drive ]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Farmington]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[CT]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[06032]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[MOVE IN READY !! Beautifully updated Colonial located in a quiet family friendly Farmington neighborhood. This two story home boasts a large back yard with impeccable lush landscaping and a private recently rebuilt deck with retractable]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[MOVE IN READY !! Beautifully updated Colonial located in a quiet family friendly Farmington neighborhood. This two story home boasts a large back yard with impeccable lush landscaping and a private recently rebuilt deck with retractable awning. Front and back yards have an in ground sprinkler system. Hardwood floors throughout the entire home with a completely refinished 900 SqFt.basement! Spacious kitchen has tile floors and granite countertops. Master bath and guest bathrooms have been upgraded with tile floors and new cabinets. This gorgeous home has central three zone a/c, electric heat and is also equipped with a central vacuum system.Ê]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://fsbo.com/listings/listings/show/id/180818/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$250,000.00]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[33 South Elm St ]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Wallingford]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[CT]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[06492]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[2 separate electric hot water tanks, off street parking, large shed, great income potential @$1200 each, can use some upgrades, will offer 2.5% to Realtor who brings buyer.]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[2 separate electric hot water tanks, off street parking, large shed, great income potential @$1200 each, can use some upgrades, will offer 2.5% to Realtor who brings buyer.]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://fsbo.com/listings/listings/show/id/182539/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$319,900.00]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[148 Everit St. Apt. A ]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[New Haven]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[CT]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[06511]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Our lovely first floor condo is nestled in the heart of the East Rock neighborhood on one of New Haven's premier streets. Freshly painted, this bright and beautiful 2-bedroom unit features a large living room, spacious dining room and eat-in k]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[Our lovely first floor condo is nestled in the heart of the East Rock neighborhood on one of New Haven's premier streets. Freshly painted, this bright and beautiful 2-bedroom unit features a large living room, spacious dining room and eat-in kitchen with breakfast nook (which we use as an office).Ê]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[http://fsbo.com/listings/listings/show/id/179695/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$1,735,000.00]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[4 Indian Spring Rd]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Norwalk]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[CT]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[06853]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[Completely renovated in 2016. Located on one of Rowayton's premiere streets with privacy & little traffic. .71 acres and an outdoor pool, which has also been fenced in and has a new pool heater. New roof in 2016. Since this house was newly renovated, the Zillow Zestimate is inaccurate and does not reflect the current home]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[Completely renovated in 2016. Located on one of Rowayton's premiere streets with privacy & little traffic. .71 acres and an outdoor pool, which has also been fenced in and has a new pool heater. New roof in 2016. Since this house was newly renovated, the Zillow Zestimate is inaccurate and does not reflect the current home value.*]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[https://www.zillow.com/homes/fsbo/Norwalk-CT/mmm_pt/58819927_zpid/26222_rid/globalrelevanceex_sort/41.507034,-72.557145,40.930633,-73.859025_rect/9_zm/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
	<node>
		<price><![CDATA[$700,000.00 ]]></price>
		<address><![CDATA[9 Cross Brook Lane]]></address>
		<city><![CDATA[Westport]]></city>
		<state><![CDATA[CT]]></state>
		<zipcode><![CDATA[06880]]></zipcode>
		<shortdescription><![CDATA[This 2400 square foot single family home has 4 bedrooms and 3.0 bathrooms. It is located at 9 Cross Brook Ln Westport, Connecticut.]]></shortdescription>
		<description><![CDATA[This 2400 square foot single family home has 4 bedrooms and 3.0 bathrooms. It is located at 9 Cross Brook Ln Westport, Connecticut.]]></description>
		<undefined7><![CDATA[]]></undefined7>
		<listingurl><![CDATA[https://www.zillow.com/homes/fsbo/Norwalk-CT/mmm_pt/58808799_zpid/26222_rid/globalrelevanceex_sort/41.507034,-72.557145,40.930633,-73.859025_rect/9_zm/]]></listingurl>
	</node>
</data>
